[
  {

    "question": "How old is Rean at the beginning of Cold Steel 1",
    "choices": ["A. 15", "B. 17", "C. 18", "D. 16"],
    "answer": 3
  }, 

  {

    "question": "What is the name of the recurring NPC who is known for failing at romance",
    "choices": ["A. Nielson", "B. Ricky", "C. Campanella", "D. Anton"],
    "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "What year does Trails from Zero take place",
      "choices": ["A. 1202", "B. 1207", "C. 1204", "D. 1210"],
      "answer": 2
  }, 

  {
      "question": "How does the SSS survive their initial encounter with Joachim",
      "choices": ["A. Estelle, Joshua and Renne help them", "B. Kevin freezes Joachim", "C. Arios saves the day", "D. They don't"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "Where does Laura place on the midterm rankings in Cold Steel 1",
      "choices": ["A. 7th", "B. 17th", "C. 20th", "D. 36th"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Which game does Gideon of the Imperial Liberation Front make his first appearance",
      "choices": ["A. Trails to Azure", "B. Cold Steel 1", "C. Cold Steel 2", "D. Trails from Zero"],
      "answer": 0
  },

  {
      "question": "Who's alias is the Black Whirlwind",
      "choices": ["A. Aurelia Le Guin", "B. Wallace Bardias", "C. Gaius Worzel", "D. Garcia Rossi"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Which of these is not a craft used by Kevin",
      "choices": ["A. Mortal Punishment", "B. Crossgear Rage", "C. Sacred Breath", "D. Infinity Sparrows"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "How many playable characters are in Trail into Reverie",
      "choices": ["A. 47", "B. 51", "C. 53", "D. 49"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Who is the youngest of these character upon their initial introduction",
      "choices": ["A. Tio Plato", "B. Tita Russell", "C. Renne Hayworth", "D. Ferida Al-Fayed"],
      "answer": 2
  },

  {
      "question": "What's the name of the ost that plays during the final boss of Trails in the Sky SC",
      "choices": ["A. Get Over the Barrier", "B. Fateful Confrontation", "C. Merciless Savior", "D. Whereabouts of Hope"],
      "answer": 2
  }
 ]